const dataset = {
    name: "wilson chu",
	levels: [],
	lastSeen: new Date(),
	deck: [
        {
            question: "The tag that contains a collection of metadata elements that describe the document or provide instructions to the browser",
            answer: "head",
            category: "html"
        },
        {
            question: "The tag that specifies an external resource that the document is connected to",
            answer: "link",
            category: "html"
        },
        {
            question: "The tag that provides programming code for programs to be run within the document",
            answer: "script",
            category: "html"
        },
        {
            question: "The tag that defines the display styles used to render the document content",
            answer: "style",
            category: "html"
        },
        {
            question: "The tag that stores the document's title or name, usually displayed in the browser title bar or on a browser tab",
            answer: "title",
            category: "html"
        },
        {
            question: "The tag that contains the entire content of the document",
            answer: "body",
            category: "html"
        },
        {
            question: "The tag that contains closing content that concludes an article or section",
            answer: "footer",
            category: "html"
        },
        {
            question: "The tag that marks a list of hypertext or navigation links",
            answer: "nav",
            category: "html"
        },
        {
            question: "The css selector that matches any of the elements elem1, elem2, etc.",
            answer: ",",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css selector that matches the child element that is a child of the parent element",
            answer: ">",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css selector that matches elem2 that is immediately preceded by the sibling element elem1",
            answer: "+",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css selector that Matches elem2 that follows the sibling element elem1",
            answer: "~",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css selector that Matches elem2 that follows the sibling element elem1",
            answer: "~",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css pseudo-class that selects the first descendant of the parent that matches the specified type",
            answer: ":first-of-type",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css pseudo-class that selects the nth element of the parent of the specified type",
            answer: ":nth-of-type(n)",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css pseudo-class that selects An element not matching the specified selector",
            answer: ":not(selector)",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css pseudo-class that selects a link that has been visited by the user",
            answer: ":visited",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css pseudo-class that selects a link when the mouse pointer is hovering over the element",
            answer: ":hover",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The css pseudo-class that selects a link when the element is receiving the focus of the keyboard or mouse pointer",
            answer: ":focus",
            category: "css"
        },
        {
            question: "The attribute that defers script processing until after the page has been completely parsed and loaded",
            answer: "defer",
            category: "js"
        },
        {
            question: "The attribute that tells a browser to parse the HTML and JavaScript code together",
            answer: "async",
            category: "js"
        },
        {
            question: "The method from the document class that reference an element using its id",
            answer: "getElementById",
            category: "js"
        },
        {
            question: "The property of an element that returns the HTML code within itself",
            answer: "innerHTML",
            category: "js"
        },
        {
            question: "The property of an element that returns the text within itself disregarding any HTML tags",
            answer: "textConent",
            category: "js"
        },
        {
            question: "The method of an element to inserts HTML code defined by 'text' at 'position'",
            answer: "insertAdjacentHTML",
            category: "js"
        },
        {
            question: "The method of a Date object that returns the year",
            answer: "getFullYear",
            category: "js"
        },
        {
            question: "The method of a Date object that returns the day of the week, where Sunday = 0, Monday = 1, etc.",
            answer: "getDay",
            category: "js"
        },
        {
            question: "The operator that returns the remainder after dividing one item by another",
            answer: "%",
            category: "js"
        },
        {
            question: "The method of the Math class that rounds x down to the next lowest integer",
            answer: "floor",
            category: "js"
        },
    ]
}

